Hello and welcome back once again everyone
good evening welcome everyone.
Who will do the big thing in your name this evening in the name of cricket
?  Pink Panthers or Predent
Warriors second some finals
the center Predent Warriors one the toss
elected to field first they invited
Pink Panthers to bat first and we have the
two batsmen already on the crease Vishram
Sakkare and Pratik Kadam and we have Ashish
Mishra to start the presides the
captain here we go three to one game on
first ball tucks it away for a single played
with soft handed covers
starts with one run
trying to stop follow through by Ashish but
they fielder admits of
one famous contender
Mangesh Jatab
both the batsmen are off the mark with a single
first two overs power play
and lets see what Vishram and Pratik how they will
capitalize first two overs
that played fine the ball is going fielder
is running and he stopped
two runs taken
with two runs here four four nolas after
three balls being bowled
and it's very good bowling from Ashish they
went for no runs
good start from Predent Warriors
and this time up and over there is a  Fielder
standing in deep
only a single
so bet of an A but safe
and slowly and steadily both the batsmen
rotating strike they need some five boxes
also one
fielder at mid wicket
that's a good strike
only a single good start by Priors
one gone six Pink Panthers
and that time played up an over very well
played four runs
Mangesh Jagtap have seen quite expensive in the last match se behold
first over completion the score
was six runs and then six runs and two
balls
single run taken 13 loss after 1.3 Pink
Panthers
setting up the field settings by Mangesh
Jagtap there is one fielder standing
at deep cover and point between them one fielder
and one at long on that's
a good bowling swing a
good come back from Mangesh Jagtap
1.4 13 for nun
and that's a good strike that will go all the way
for four runs very well played a good
pickup shot from Vishram
outside the offm line and cut away  Nicely over
the fielder at deep backward point for four
runs
17 runs with that boundary 17 for no loss
Pink Panthers
last ball of this over proved to be expensive 11
runs have been given here Mangesh
and once again is this a copy paste of the previous
ball four runs and
powerful brilliant stalwart Vishram
21 runs after two overs no wicket Pink
Panthers
tour gone 21 for no loss
and good start from the opening pair
Vishram and Pratik.  So that's the end of the
power play.  Maximum fielders can be go
outside the circle but minimum four fielders
should be inside the circle.
This time the game has been played outside the border
and one four Pratik and Vishram, now their
car will stop directly in Delhi and the
plane has also landed exactly there.  Now
the plane will go from Mumbai to Delhi.  Pratik and Vishram will
get tickets for the final match.
So 2.1 25 for no loss.
Chetan Kadam and the Binge Attack.  First ball four
runs
and good batting good start from Prak
Kadam and Vishram the opening, something change
in the field settings
deep point fielder inside circle ultiple
shot and look this is innovation what a thing,
excellent powerful brilliant four
this is modern cricket you will get to see such matches, such
shots, strange cricket four
runs back to back here number four
29 for no loss
so one
il one team has already entered the final now it is a fierce battle between both the teams
who will win will
enter the final of the ICICI Lambars
Brocos Premier League two and two six season
three
this time the ball is going,
fielder is present at deep backward square leg
excellent stop there
suddenly Jonty Rhodes in the frame from
nowhere.   There was a
lot of experience content, Jonty Rhodes,
Deaf Duplessis, Glenn Maxwell in morning cricket,
Glenn Phillips, all from
New Zealand.
Good Fielding
and Legendary Fielders Across the World.
Big appeal this time
but no contact, bat and ball
2.431 for loss, Ping Panthers have made a
good comeback this time,
Chetan Kadam proved a bit expensive
in the beginning
but he made a comeback, giving away
eight runs in the first two balls and then
only three runs in the next three balls.  So this is the
comeback made by Chetan Kadam in this over.
Excellent bowling, excellent bowling, totally
impressed the batsman here.
32 runs, no wickets after three overs.  Three Pathars
Three was gone 32 for none Vivek Pawar in the
attack
just going backward and playing it
softly Mangesh Jagtap the fielder at long off only
single
Pratik Kadam 21 off 11 three fours and
Vishram Sakkare 12 off adv two fours
War is looking for the first wicket
and that's a clever bowling from Vivek
Pawar
keeping away from the batters arc so he will
not hit for a big one that's a good
strategy from Vivek Pawar there could have been a
chance of run out but he misfielded
and Mangesh has to be praised here Mangesh went from
mid on to long off to deep
extra cover as a backup fielder it
is very important to have this backup in cricket.   I will
take two runs here.
This time there could be a threat and the first wicket could be kept.
Prent Warriors was looking for that
first wicket and finally they got it.
And Vivek Pawar is again a lucky charm for the
team.
And suddenly the throw was like Ravindra Jadeja
from nowhere
last ball coming up just five runs conceded
by Vivek Pawar
inside edge
the keeper has
not stopped that ball
one run to end of the over four go on 38 for
one Pink Panthers now we have to see in the coming four overs if we
bat with this strategy then we will
set a score of 80 here
now Pink Panthers
and that is a good strike and this is the
disadvantage of tennis ball that if you let it bounce
in the deep fielder then the ball will go over him.
At 42 for four, Pink Panthers'
Pratik Kadam is batting brilliantly. 28 off
14 balls with four fours and has
made room once. The ball is in play.
Fielders are running towards fine leg. The ball is going.
Fielders are running to stop it.
Two runs will be scored here.
Only a single on 44, good bowling from Ashish
Mishra, the skipper of Priors,
and this time he has played the ball in the air
over the fielder for six runs. With this six runs,
Pink Panthers have completed 50 runs.
50 up
heads. What a shot from Rahul Sawant.
Excellent powerful sixer on the first ball
over mid-wicket
and he has lifted it once, is it out? Will he
catch the wicket this time?
Rahul Sawant hit the
previous ball for six and was very happy with himself.
Look at the frustration level, it tells you
how valuable the wicket was there.
This pink purse has lost it.
That's a second wicket fall and Ashish Mishra (
Captain) strikes.  LookingToConnect
found height but not length.
4.5 51 on two
o That's very good bowling and to the block
hole.
So that's the end of the over five was gone 51
for two Pink Panthers and coming up three
overs of the first innings Pratik Kadam will have to
give more strike here to
Ramesh and Ramesh will play an anchor role and
Pratik Kadam will go for some quick wickets
and here comes the fall of wicket number three good
stumping by Nitin 5.2 52 off three Pink
Panthers
52 for three the new batsman
Hemant
and that's a good strike high in the air
and will wait for the umpire signal is that
boundary and six
for Runs that's four Runs
56 for three
good shot high in the air fielder tries his
level best but went for four Hemant off the
mark first ball boundary wow
stretching himself sliding for a
single run two runs in and
good running
58 off three with two runs
and this time he has lifted the ball in the air
going for two runs
and two runs with ease and once again we will complete
60 off three last ball of this over
Vivek Pawar nine runs so far
60 for three in this over
dancing down the track straight off the fielder
but a single run they will take end of the over
six gone 61 for three Pink Panthers and
coming up last two overs of the first
innings
you are watching ICSAB
Proudly presenting Brokers Premier
League 2 Season Three the time final two already we have
finalists one finalist all one
team they are waiting one I one team is
waiting which team will come
in the final and will challenge us we have to
see
Panthers or Warriors
what a shot
but well taken there at cow corner
looking to connect for a big one
and a good catch taken at cow corner fielder
standing there and that's a one more wicket
fall of Pink Panthers
Mangesh Jagtab strikes catch taken by
Kiran Hemant Ambekar departs 95 win 4
6.161 for four Pink Panthers
the new batter Pratik Bhandari and chance for the
one more catch oh he took that would you believe it
catch  Taken at the second attempt and Mangesh Jagtap has got to back
to the wicket two wickets here
and Mangesh Jagtap is on a hat-trick
quite a long journey from Pune to Mumbai to
bowl this now he will get a hat-trick
61 for five 6.2 Pink Panthers
what a cash from Chetan
Chetan can't say clever Chetan can say
61 one for five a new batter Vikas Shukla has
pushed it with light hands.   I'll take
one run here.
And this time he has lifted the ball and it has gone into the sky.  The
ball has touched the stars
and this catch went to create
big fireworks but got out.
One wicket for Pink Panthers and Mangesh
Jagtap
and this time played towards covers region that will
run away for four runs
able to stop in the follow through
will update the score as soon as it is get
updated.
Will update the latest score after getting
updated from the scorer.
From go 67 for six
seven go on 67 for six last over coming
up of the first innings Vikas Shukla and
Amol Kolte on the cuz
play towards long on they going for two
runs
and the throw is not that fine two runs taken
69 for six
and that's gone miles in the air Mangesh
Undneet he takes it one more
wicket fall seven
wickets down Pink Panthers and Prudent
Warriors restricting here a
big score here Pink Panthers
would like to make
69 for from Amit Garj departs
Alok Pandey the new batter
coming at number nine
Akshay to Mr Pandey
total beaten here.  Excellent bing
and catch has been put down
7.4 71 for from last two balls and this time
high in the fielder that will land save and one
bounce in to the fence for four runs
if you let the ball bounce then the
ball will go over you and the same thing happened
twice thrice in this innings that is a
disadvantage of tennis ball it really
bounces a lot last ball of the innings
coming up 7.5 75 for from last ball of the
first innings
and that is stump out.  So, eight overs have gone 75
for eight down and 76 is a target to chase
for Prodigious Warriors.  See you after a short break.  Till then,
hot tea and samosas.
Send it to the commentary box.  Thank you very much.
Hello and welcome back once again.  Semi-final
to target of 76 to chase and here we go the
first ball
first ball for a single run quickly
or Krishnajeet Singh and Akshay on the chase 76 chase
a big target
front Warriors whoever wins the match
will enter the final v one and one team
good excellent shot cracking hit
chairman of that Rahul Sawant
I have not got hurt here but I
hit as hard as I did Krishnajeet
four balls two runs no wicket Warriors
this time got totally
beaten
five balls two runs
no wicket good start here
Rahul Sawant
good
big appeal here some
discussion has taken place here.   The
square leg umpire said not out
and umpire's signal umpire's decision will
file decision
so only two runs one was gone for no loss
and that's very well played.  That will
go all the way for four runs.
Krishanjeet Singh and Akshay Talekar
and that's what they needed first over only it was to
run
and now Krishanjeet Singh one of the strongest
contenders of the team Warriors
and that's a good strike high in the air.
That will go all the way for four runs.
So back to back Krishanjeet Singh on fire.
And out of the dugout the Proud Warriors are cheering
and that's what all the spectate supporters
coming from Priors
and that's high in the air one bounce to the
fielder at square going for two runs
64 from 6.3
Silence in the dugout of Pink Panthers but it's
a cheering crowd from Priors Woh kehte hain
cricket ka khel pal me tola pal me masha Kabhi Khushi Kabhie Gham Kaun Banega
Match Ka
Singham
Krishanjeet Singh and Akshay Talekar
and both batsmen
and that's good bowling change in big
variation swing n miss
to go 13 for no loss six overs needed 63
runs
and this time high in the air and drop I
think there is something magic in the
Proud Warriors supporters
the chance has been put down once again something
going on on the field roller
coaster Pink Panthers Warriors
and we are the big contenders Mangesh Jagtap
Mr MJ
what a match this is still the excitement
is on both the teams
55 runs in 5.9 This time high in the air
that's gone but the fielder has taken that catch
and a big wicket
that's Krishanjeet Singh a big fish in to the
pavilion
21 for two down
three overs gone 21 for two prone Warriors
need 55 runs in five overs 11 runs per over
so three go 21 for two and five overs 55
setting up the field Pink Panthers
Across the iconic big ground of Fatima
Grounds Vidya We are Mumbai.
We are calling ourselves Lords of Mumbai.
O Mangesh Jagtap
and Nitin Nikam are the two new batsmen at the
crease.
And Pratik Kadam Wow.
Wow fantastic who you believe it switch hit
for six runs Mr. MJ for you
class best toast delivery palti palti de
ghuma ke jio player wow wow he
is a great player for six runs Mr. MJ Mangesh does
such fireworks he makes the ball
travel directly from Mumbai to Pune without ticket
and once
wide
decision by the umpire there is
a special announcement for Mangesh.
At 3:27 there is
a special announcement: If Mangesh Jagtap
wins this match,
he will receive a special bat from Vivek Pawar.  Let's give
a big round of applause to Vivek Pawar ji.
So President Warriors chased the target of 76
given and 28 for 2 in 48 runs and 4.4 overs in 28
balls and 48 runs. What was that
good bowling from Pratik
Kadam
looking to swing the bat
trying to spin the ball Pratik Kadam once again
looking to play across the line
mistimed completely
and looking to play that switch it once again very
good bowling from Pratik Kadam just
seven runs conceded
good comeback after he got hit second ball
six then and wide and three dot balls
back to back.
And that will go.  Good stop.  Very good
stop there.
Two Rans Taken.  End of the over.
Two runs for 30 after four overs and 46 runs needed in four overs.
Once again welcome back
the semi final two is in progress we already got
the one finalist one and one team
icic brokers premier league two and two six
season three saturday
sunday cricketing vibes
many of spectators they cancelled
the weekend destination
holiday and they cancelled because of this two days
of the exciting contest correct sir long
wicket
those who had booked hotels
holidays they cancelled a ticket and
coming to enjoy this match
down the leg side for wide
this is what the love and support for the team
to all the spectators joining on in the
YouTube channel.  Thank you very much for the
support from yesterday and today.
After this match we have one more match for the
third position.  Loser semi-final one and loser
semi-final two will play against each other for
the third place and this time that will go all the way
for four runs
Dhandhani Khankhnit Chaukar
That's Nitin Nikam very first ball
strikes
41 runs in 3.5 overs That's
23 balls and 41 runs
and that's a good strike that will go all the way
for four runs Wow back to back boundaries
and the dugout is dancing on their feet
Present Warriors
on fire Nitin and now after Mangesh now Nitin
good start
fireworks in the first two balls on Nitin Nikam Parash
Parshuram
Parshuram need to come back and that's leg bye from
umpire Mr Fariyaz Shaikh
and we have switched Master Mangesh Jagtap AK
MJ
36 runs and 21 balls 21 balls 36 runs
Looking for a big connect
Timing Time Couldn't make it Excellent bowling
by Ashram there
35 runs needed in 20 balls  In.
35 runs in 20 balls.
Down the leg side for a wide and plus one run
to extra Coming up
43 for two Needed 33 runs in 20 balls
Couple of big hits from Prudent Warriors will make
an impact
Mangesh Jagata One strike
Look at the side of Parshuram
Just conceded
Single
and no runs
Single run taken
Last ball of the fifth over 44
No runs taken End of the over
Five gone 44 for two and
needed 32 runs in three overs Three overs gone 32 they needed
now in the next three overs
32 runs in 18 balls
Five gone 44
Need 32 runs in three overs
Captain in the side attack
and that's gone fine That will go all the way
for six runs I believe that's four runs
but still they will check
four That's
four runs and 28 from 17
and that's gone high into the sky
from Mumbai skylines to the Pune skylines
and these seven
balls directly
22  Runs needed in 16 balls.   22
off 16 balls
what a hit what a shot Mangesh Jagtap at his
best
20 of 10 1426
dangerous man like Andre Russell
one big hit they need more one big hit to
get the equation closer 22 runs and 16 balls
oh good bowling from Hemant Mangesh thought the ball will
go down the leg side but hitting on his
body
on his back went for a dot ball 22 off 15 balls
15 balls 22 and Hemant captain to Mangesh
and that's a good strike they will go for the
running first hard going for the second run
this could be the big wicket is it out
Mangesh Jagtap he departs
and why are they going for two runs
because they are well set the equation is not that
far but it's like the big fish into the pavilion
21 needed from now
14 balls 5.4 55 for two
21 runs 14  Balls
The new batter
Ashish Mishra The captain now walks in
and the player resumes
21 runs and 14 balls.
Jayesh Gandhi new bat Nitin Nikam
lets end of the over six gone it's 55 for
three needed in two overs 21 runs
so 21 runs in 12 balls all eyes on Jayesh Gandhi
all eyes on now
Rahul Sawant
in the big attack only two runs conceded in the
first over
Nitin on strike
that's going outside the off line for a wide
20 runs needed in 12 balls at 10 runs per
over
play simple, keep it simple and win simple.
20 runs in 12 balls
Rahul to Jayesh and Nitin
just a single.
Jayesh on strike,
19 runs needed from 11 balls.   We'll have to
see if it's inside edge or 22
inside edge bats here.
Be lucky.  One run taken here
in the backward region.  18 runs in 10 balls.
Preet Warriors or Pink Panthers, who will
enter the final with one all, one team is
waiting, which of these two
teams will come and challenge us and that's a
good strike, only a single run,
good field setup,
see the bowling of Rahul Sawant, one over,
only three runs, one over, three balls, only six runs given,
17 runs are needed now in nine balls,
left right combination
and that will burn the calories of the fielders,
one at long on, one at cow corner and one
at mid wicket on side, three fielders,
mid wicket and square leg between them, one
fielder,
just a single run, good bowling from from,
Rahul Sawant is defending here completely,
giving only one run each.  Back to
back four singles
16 runs in eight balls One big hit will make an
impact Directly
a big hit and will make the match a superhit
or back to back two wickets here Rahul
Sawant will change the game completely
On strike double n Nitin Nikam
and this time he has played only
one run Wanted to go for the second run
but is satisfied with one run Excellent
over Only six runs so far in five balls and
15 needed in seven balls
What a match what a match Semi-final to
live from Fatima Grounds
Vidhya Mumbai here we go
Last ball of the penultimate over
Jasprit Bumrah is like Bing's over
Reminded of Jasprit Bumrah's over
Jayesh on strike
and Jayesh has gone for a big one There is a
fielder They are going for two runs and this is going to
ping Panthers
on the money
Important breakthrough Need 14 runs in six balls.
14 runs in six balls.  What a match are
you watching ICICI Lumberjack
presenting
Bros Premier League 2 and 2 six season
three semi-final is on You already got
one finalist One and one team
The Orange Army and Let's Win Army
Proud Warriors and Pink Panthers Will
Join The Party Win
Team
Tension Rising Heart is Beating
Dil ki dhaan aap gayi The breath has stopped The
weather has changed all around
A bit of tension is rising in the dug Also
excitement is getting doubled
14 runs and six balls
Chetan Kadam Jayesh Gandhi
Kaun Banega Baazigar Kaun Kahlaega Muqaddar Ka
Sikandar
14 runs six balls S choo 14 runs Garaj Proud
Warriors Na ha saamna jena sa
And the last over is at Vikas Shukla will
bowl Here we go
Chetan Kadam on strike
14 runs six balls Something has changed in the
field setting
Deep square leg is brought back inside the
circle square leg Oh no they have one more
Field setup remaining from deep Keep
backward square leg
The fielder  Standing at cover shot
and that's a good strike high in the air
safe and they are going for two runs and two runs
taken
12 runs needed in five balls
and this time which government
five balls and 12 runs
all the spectators are prudent warriors
standing on the feet they are not able to settle
down
five balls 12
and B Chetan Kadam
Jayesh Gandhi retired now new batsman
and that's a good strike
and they are going for two runs
and they will get two runs
10 runs in four balls
a big hit has to be made.   The
ball must reach a new cross.  The ball has to be
sent across
space into the constellation
10 runs in four balls
and that's a good strike.
O taken that guard would you believe it.
Wow well taken.  This could be the game changing
moment for the team Pink Panthers.
Excellent catch.  Went to take a shot.   There
was definitely height but the length got a little short
and the wicket fell
and the way he tried here Chetan
Kadam
cash by Ramesh
needs 10 runs in three balls
10 runs three balls Nimesh Patil
and and only a single they will get.
Nine runs in two balls, a big hit
is essential
as victory is assured.  It is necessary to hit six runs.
One dot ball will be the match on for Pink
Panthers.  One big hit,
only a single, so one fair delivery will be
the match and now it will be a mere formality
for Britain Wars, no no ball,
no wide ball,
one ball eight runs,
one fair delivery, even
if six runs are scored, there will be
no threat to the Pink Panthers.  Here we go.
And that's the victory
Pink Panthers
are going into the grand finale with One Oil
One Team but also we can appreciate the
performance from Prideful Warriors.
He displayed excellent game performance in
this historic ground of Mumbai,
Fatima Grounds Vidya